好了 最后一个部件
All right,that's the last servo.
人家看到的 是全方位运动 销毁终结切割器
Behold the Mobile Omnidirectional Neutralization and Termination Eradicator.
或者 Mont-E
Or...MONTE.
装有铰接式锋利锯齿 聚碳酸脂磨刀和转动轮
Featuring one articulated razor-sharp killing saw,one polycarbonate grinding and flipping wheel,
从上到下为钢制金属板外壳 其马力足以将110磅的机械
steel-armor plate exoskeleton top and bottom,and enough horsepower to drive a 110 pounds of mechanized death
彻底毁灭 只需短短4.8秒
from zero to holy crap in 4.8 seconds.
如果说我爱我们的机器人杀手 是不是大罪过?
Is it wrong to say I love our killer robot?
跟对我爸爸一样 我既爱它又怕它
As with my father,I both love and fear it.
好了 废话少说 我们来搞点破坏
All right,enough chitchat. Let's destroy something.
1 2 3
1,2,3
好了 让谁先来尝尝猛械的厉害
Okay. What shall be first to taste the wrath of Monte?
也许我们该从小的东西开始
*************
好吧 也许今天我们最终可以搞清楚 这个魔法球里有什么了
**************
我四岁时就做过了
Did it when I was four.
是个二十面体染色物在蓝水里漂浮
It's an icosahedral dye floating in tinted blue water.
老兄 说之前给个"剧透"警告好吧
Man,call "spoiler alert" before you say things like that.
烤面包机怎么样?
How about the toaster oven?
烤面包机咋得罪你了?
What did the toaster oven ever do to you?
三年级时 我又咋得罪吉姆·马林斯了?
What did I ever do to Jimmy Mullins in the third grade?
他照样用我的拳头朝我的脸打了一拳
He still punched me in the face with my own fists.
抱歉 可爱的小呆子 你在错误的时间出现错误的房间
Sorry,you little nerd,you were just in the wrong boys' room at the wrong time.
同志们 护眼镜
Gentlemen,goggles.
这可是个历史性的时刻
This is an auspicious moment.
制造第一枚核武器和第一次登月
就像罗伯特·奥本海默和尼尔·阿姆斯壮
Like Robert Oppenheimer or Neil Armstrong,
我们得编句合适的台词 来纪念这个有历史意义的科学事件
we need the appropriate words to mark this historic scientific event.
"死吧 烤面包机 去死吧!"怎么样?
How about "Die,toaster,die"?
我看行
That'll do it.
好啦 接下来砍什么?
All right,what's next?
不了 我今晚要呆在家里洗衣服
No,I think I'm just going to stay in tonight and do laundry.
《生活大爆炸》
第二季  第12集
噢 耶 这门被猛械毁了
Oh,yeah,this door got the full Monte.
莱纳德?
Leonard?
怎么回事?
What the hell?
机器人杀手 我们造的
Killer robot. We built it.
是吗 它差点杀了我
Yeah,well,it almost killed me.
它要是想杀你 你早死了
If it wanted to kill you,you'd be dead.
那么 它到底想杀谁?
So,who exactly does it want to kill?
抱歉 难道你不知道即将举行的 南加州机器人格斗循环邀请赛?
I'm sorry,are you unaware of the upcoming Southern California Robot Fighting League Round Robin Invitational?
知道吗 从我去年搬来以后 不是所有的邮件都被转寄掉
You know,since I moved last year,not all my mail has been forwarded.
这可是件大事
It's a big deal.
会有颁奖宴会还有舞会
There's an awards banquet and a dance afterward.
也许你会想跟我一起去
Perhaps you'd like to come with me.
我相信其他人看见女生 肯定会很兴奋
I know the other fellas would be really excited to see a girl there.
如果就我一个女生去 怎么能叫舞会呢?
How is it supposed to be a dance if I'm the only girl?
好吧 也许这么说有点夸张
Well,that may be a slight exaggeration.
你是唯一可以上的女孩
You'd be the only doable girl.
你是头猪 霍华德
You're a pig,Howard.
"可以上"是在赞美你 没别的意思
How is "doable" anything but a compliment?
霍华德 我们还是搞机器人吧
Howard,why don't we just work on the robot?
拜托 莱纳德 现在不是时候
Please,Leonard,not now.
又一次 佩妮和我开始了 我们的双人探戈
Once again,Penny and I have begun our little tango.
我们的探戈?
Our tango?
肉体的博弈 性欲的推拉
The carnal repartee,the erotic to and fro.
尽管开胃菜很美味
But as delicious as the appetizer might be,
我们还是该屈从 吃下主菜 趁它还是...
at some point we will have to succumb and eat the entr\e while it's still...
热的
hot.
求你了 不要再说了
I'm begging you,stop talking.
听着 通常呢 我无视你就好了
Look,normally I can just ignore you.
我知道 你有点古怪
I mean,I get it-- you're a little peculiar.
就像谢尔顿
You know,like Sheldon.
抱歉 佩妮 但是在这间屋里 你才是古怪的那个
Excuse me,Penny,but in this room,you're the one who's peculiar.
嗯 也许你说的对
Yeah,you might be right.
但是回到你身上
But back to you.
我知道你认为自己是个 能言善辩的少女杀手
I know you think you're some sort of smooth-talking ladies' man,
但事实是 你很可悲又恶心
but the truth is,you are just pathetic and creepy.
那么 啥意思呢?
So what are you saying?
我的意思是说我是"可以上的" 根本就不是啥赞美
I am saying it is not a compliment to call me "doable."
盯着我的屁股看并说 "喔~ 这肯定是果冻"
It's not sexy to stare at my ass and say,Ooh,
"因为果酱不会这样晃动" 一点也不性感
it must be jelly 'cause jam don't shake like that.
还有最重要的 我们没有在跳探戈 我们没有你推我拉
And most important,we are not dancing a tango,we're not to'ing and fro'ing.
我们之间不会有什么 永远不会
Nothing is ever going to happen between us. Ever.
等一下 这不是在调情 你在说真的?
Wait a minute. This isn't flirting. You're serious.
调情? 你认为我在跟你调情?
Flirting? You think I'm flirting with you?
我根本没有在和你调情
I am not flirting with you.
没有女人会和你调情
No woman is ever gonna flirt with you.
你只会慢慢变老 孤独而终
You're just gonna grow old and die alone.
谢谢你的提醒
Thanks for the heads up.
霍华德 你去哪里?
Howard,where you going?
我回家继续过我的 恶心的可悲的人生
I'm going home to live my creepy,pathetic life.
总得有人说吧
Well,someone had to say it.
什么?
What?
他说也许我们该拿你参加机器人杀手大赛
He said maybe we should enter you in the killer robot competition.
霍华德 电话在响!
Howard,the phone is ringing!
我有个疯狂的主意 老妈 接电话如何!
Here's a crazy idea,Ma: Answer it!
你好?
Hello?
好的 稍等
All right,hold on.
是你朋友 莱纳德!
It's your friend,Leonard!
他想知道你为什么今天没去上学!
He wants to know why you're not at school today!
我不是去上学 老妈 我在大学就职
I don't go to school,Ma. I work at a university.
那就是学校! 快接电话!
That's a school! Now pick up the phone!
我谁都不想理
I don't want to talk to anybody.
要我叫莱纳德把你的家庭作业带来吗?
Should I ask Leonard to bring over your homework? !
我没什么家庭作业的
I don't have homework.
我是个拥有工程学硕士的大爷们
I'm a grown man with a master's degree in engineering!
抱歉 了不起先生
Excuse me,Mr. Fancy-Pants.
想吃冰棒吗?
Want me to get you a Popsicle?
樱桃味的 好吧!
Cherry,please!
樱桃味的我吃了 只剩蔬菜味的了
I ate the cherry. All that's left is green.
你让我真想自杀呀
You make me want to kill myself.
怎么了?
What's going on?
不知道 他们正为冰棒问题吵呢
I don't know,now they're just yelling about Popsicles.
好像佩妮真地伤到他了
Sounds like Penny really got to him.
我觉得不意外呀
I'm not surprised.
尽管霍华德用坚强的外壳来保护自己 其实他是个非常敏感的人
Despite his hard and crusty shell,Howard is a very sensitive man.
知道他还写诗吗?
Do you know he writes poetry?
大多是关于来自楠塔基特岛的人 和叫戴维的隐居士
Mostly about men from Nantucket and hermits named Dave,
但他是用心去写的
but he does it with real sensitivity.
嘿 霍夫施塔特
Hey,Hofstadter.
等离止誓验室 谣传你们在造机器银
Word around the pwasma wab is you built a wobot?
对 我们造了 克里帕奇
Yes,we did,Kripke.
他名叫猛械
His name is Monte.
如果你着梦操控他来 南加州机器银格斗循环邀请晒
Well,if you have any dewusions about entering him against my wobot,
对抗我克里帕奇 克里骇人的机器银
the Kwipke Kwippler in the Southern California Robot Fighting League Wound Wobin Invitational,
又简称S.c.r.f.l.r.r.i
aka the S.C.R.F.L.R.R.I.,
他就该改名叫金属废物银了
his name is gonna be Swrap Metal.
得了吧 真的非要这样吗?
Come on,is that really necessary?
莱纳德 看来需要的
Leonard,I believe it is.
这是上场前嘴上较劲 是所有竞技的传统部分
This is trash talk,and trash talk is a traditional component in all sporting events.
克里帕奇 你的机器人很差劲 会败在我们的脚下
Kripke,your robot is inferior and it will be defeated by ours
因为我们在设计与做工上都超越你
because ours exceeds yours in both design and execution.
还有 我听说你老妈是肥婆
Also,I'm given to understand that your mother is overweight.
哇 够狠呀
Oh,snap.
当然 如果是腺分泌的关系 而没有懒散和贪食
Now,of course,if that is the result of a glandular condition and not sloth and gluttony,
我收回我的批判
I withdraw that comment.
哪有什么区别?胖还是胖呀
What difference does it make? Fat is fat.
有分界线的
There are boundaries.
听好了 忘了S.c.r.f.l.r.r.i.
Tell you what,forget the S.C.R.F.L.R.R.I.
偶棉来个机器银一对一吧
Wet's settle this woboto a woboto.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
循环晒上我们不一定碰得上
There's no guarantee we're gonna go against each other in the Wound Wobin,
咱现在就对决吧
so let's throw down.
要是怕怕就算鸟
You know,unless you're afwaid.
我们接受你的挑战 定个时间和地点吧
We accept your challenge. Name a time and place.
明天 3:00 动力学实验室
Tomorrow,3:00,the kinetics wab.
就这么说定了
Make it so.
不 别定下来 贝瑞 我们明天不能和你战斗
No,don't make it so. Barry,we can't fight you tomorrow.
我们的工程师崩溃了
Our engineer is incapacitated.
他怎么了?
What's wrong with him?
他可悲又古怪 找不到女人 所以他抑郁了
He's depressed because he's pathetic and creepy and can't get girls.
我们都可悲又古怪 找不到女人
We're all pathetic and cweepy and can't get girls.
所以我们才玩机器银格斗
That's why we fight wobots.
如果不出现 就等着当笑柄吧
If you're not there,you'll be exposed to widicule.
我很好奇 他这说的是啥方言啊?
I'm curious,what part of America is that accent from?
嘿 有时间吗?
Hey,you got a minute?
有 进来吧 啥事呢?
Yeah,come on in. What's up?
- 我需要你去给霍华德道... - 滚出去
- I need you to apologize to How... - Get out.
行行好吧 沃尔伍兹不肯出来 我们的机器人大战需要他呀
Come on. Wolowitz won't come out of his house and we need him for a robot battle.
那让机器人找他去
Well,then have the robot go and get him.
机器人又没伤他自尊
The robot didn't hurt his feelings.
他就是欠骂
His feelings needed to be hurt.
他躺在床上两天了
He's been in bed for two days.
那也好 可能是和充气娃娃玩呢
Yeah,probably with a blow-up doll.
他没有和...
He's not with a...
他和谁在一起玩真的重要吗?
Does it really matter who or what he's with?
那家伙崩溃了
The guy is devastated.
请问 我怎么可能把霍华德弄崩溃?
Oh,please,how could I possibly devastate Howard?
好吧 我不是批评你
Okay,don't take this as a criticism,
但你有时会发生暴露在致命的 伽马射线之下那种状况
but you kind of have that overexposed-to-gamma-rays thing going on.
那啥意思?
What does that mean?
比如 大多数时候 你是和气的你
You know,like,most of the time,you're the easygoing Bruce Banner,
但当你生气时 就好像变成了...
but then,when you get angry,you kind of turn into,like,you know...
成熊了?
I turn into a bear?
不是吧? 伽马射线? 你?
Seriously? Gamma rays? Bruce Banner?
这都联想不到绿巨人?
You didn't get The Incredible Hulk from that?
没关系 只是请你去和他谈谈
Never mind. Just,please go talk to him.
说啥呀? 说我并不是那个意思 可我就是那个意思呀
And say what? That I didn't mean it,because I meant it.
也许你可以从另外一个角度来谈 比如 嗯
Well,maybe you can go at it from a different angle,like,um,
你在他身上看到善良的闪光点 你那天那么说只是
you see a glimmer of goodness in him and you only said what you said
因为你想鼓舞它 让它放大闪光
because you want to nurture it and make it shine.
好吧 试试这个方法呢
Okay,let's try it this way.
还记得我们邂逅那天
Remember the day that we first met
你让我去你男朋友家里 替你把电视要回来
and you asked me to go to your boyfriend's apartment to get your TV back
他有九英尺高 把我裤子都扒了 然后你说...
and he was nine feet tall and he took my pants off and you said...
什么来着? 你说什么来着?
What was that? What did you say?
噢 对了 你说你欠我个人情
Oh,yes. You said you owed me one.
嗷 得了吧 这不公平
Okay,come on,that's not fair.
我没穿裤子就回家了
I came home with no pants.
得 我明天去一趟
Fine,I'll go over there tomorrow.
多谢
Thank you.
我该提醒你 要当心他妈妈
I should probably give you a heads up about his mother.
她怎么了?
What about her?
她是个讨喜的人 你会爱上她的
She's a delightful woman. You'll love her.
霍华德 有个叫帕西的金发女郎来找你!
Howard,there's a blonde girl,Patsy,here to see you!
谁?
Who?
噢 这回她又说自己叫佩妮
Okay,now she's saying it's Penny.
我不想同她说话
I don't want to talk to her.
妈!
Ma!
她径自跑了过去
She ran past me.
我应该把她扑倒?
Was I supposed to tackle her?
呃 我只是过来看看你怎么样了
So,I just came by to see how you were doing.
我没事
I'm fine.
很好 你妈妈看上去不错
Good. Your mom seems nice.
她坐公车的时候 别人都离她远远的
People move away from her on the bus.
有何贵干?
What do you want?
好 听着 霍华德 我是来道歉的
Okay,look. Howard,I just want to apologize.
为我说的一些话道歉
For some things that I have said.
关于你的话
About you.
有人告诉我说你也是有感情的
I've been informed that you have feelings.
而显而易见的是 我伤害了它们
And apparently,I have hurt them.
所以 我很抱歉
So,I'm sorry.
霍华德
Howard.
好 你很抱歉 再见了
Fine. You're sorry. Good-bye.
那么... 你还好吧?
So... you're okay?
嘿 我是个大男孩
Hey,I'm a big boy.
我不会因为某个女人的 随意评论而受创伤的
I'm not traumatized by some random comment from some random woman.
我是说 你别臭美了
I mean,get over yourself.
好 那么 再见了
Okay. Well,bye.
就差一点儿
So close.
噢 我的天呐 那是克里帕奇的机器人?
Oh,my God. That's Kripke's robot?
如你所见 克里骇人正把这辆 雪佛兰跑车史得粉碎
As you can see,the Kwippler is weducing the Chevy Cavawier to wubble.
我不能再看下去了
I can't watch anymore.
谢尔顿 我们得叫停它
Sheldon,we have to call it off.
没有这个选项
We don't have that option.
我们接受了挑战
We've accepted the challenge.
我们不能临阵退缩
We can't run away from a fight.
噢 得了吧 我们不是一直 都在临阵退缩么
Oh,please,we've spent our whole lives running away from fights.
个人而言 我都能从比我小一半的 篱笆墙当中找个洞钻过去
Personally,I can squeeze through a hole in a fence half my size.
你说的可能没错 但猛械可不是我们
Impressive as that may be,Monte is not us.
猛械无所畏惧
Monte has no fear.
谢尔顿 难道我们看的不是同一个录像?
Sheldon,did we all not just watch the same video?
克里帕奇的机器人刚刚虐完一辆中型汽车
Kripke's robot just had angry sex with a mid-sized automobile.
但你忽视了一个事实 我们已经对敌人了如指掌
You are overlooking the fact that we now know what we're up against
所以我们可以改装猛械 让他做好迎战的准备
and we can modify Monte so that he's prepared.
你想让他做好准备?
You want to prepare him?
给他装个膀胱再穿条短裤 他就可以吓得尿裤子了
Install a bladder and a pair of shorts so he can wet himself.
抱歉 不过没有沃尔伍兹 我们怎么进行改装?
Excuse me,but how are we going to make any modifications without Wolowitz?
- 佩妮那有信了没? - 还没
- Have you heard from Penny yet? - Not yet.
打起自信来 先生们 我们不需要沃尔伍兹帮忙
Have faith,gentlemen. We don't need Wolowitz.
工程学只是物理学 发育迟缓的小弟罢了
Engineering is merely the slow younger brother of physics.
瞧好了 学着点
Watch and learn.
你们俩有谁知道怎么开工具箱么?
Do either of you know how to open the toolbox?
之后 在我十四岁的时候 我遇见了马尔西·格罗斯曼
And then,when I was 14,I met Marcy Grossman.
她是拉摸美丽
She was so beautiful.
她刚摘掉牙套 但还是有点龅牙
She just got her braces off but they left a little of the overbite.
真是火辣
It was so hot.
就像只性感的小花栗鼠
Like a sexy little chipmunk.
我没有勇气约她出来
I didn't have the courage to ask her out,
但我在初三的才艺表演上 给她献了一首歌
but I dedicated a song to her at the ninth grade talent show.
喔 真贴心
Aw,that sounds sweet.
* 马尔西·格罗斯曼就是阴天的 *
* Marcy Grossman is sunshine *
* 一缕阳光 *
* On a cloudy day *
* 在天寒地冻时 *
* When it's cold outside *
* 马尔西·格罗斯曼就是那热情的五月 *
* Marcy Grossman is the month of May *
噢 真是可爱
Oh,it's cute.
* 我猜你会说 *
* I guess you'd say *
* 什么才能让我有这种感觉 *
* What can make me feel this way *
* 马尔西·格罗斯曼,马尔西·格罗斯曼,马尔西·格罗斯曼 *
* Marcy Grossman,Marcy Grossman,Marcy Grossman *
- * 谈论着马尔西 * - 真棒
* Talkin' 'bout Marcy * That's great.
* 格罗斯曼 *
* Grossman.*
噢 真有意思
Oh,it's fun.
然后她撅着那张性感的花栗鼠小嘴
And then she came up with that sexy little chipmunk mouth
朝我头发上淬了口唾沫
and spit in my hair.
之后就是高一的事了
Which brings us to tenth grade.
霍华德 你觉不觉得有时 自己太心急太过火了?
Howard,do you think maybe sometimes you try too hard?
看看我嘛
Look at me.
太心急太过火 我怎么可能会有机会?
What chance do I have if I don't try too hard?
这... 你的机会大大的有
Well... you'd have a terrific chance.
你聪明风趣 又有份好工作
I mean,you're smart,you're funny. You have a cool job.
你做那个飞到外太空的东西
You build stuff that goes into outer space.
也是啊
I guess.
跟你说哦 我认识你也有一年半了
Look,I'm telling you,I've known you for,like,a year and a half
这次我才觉得我是在跟你真人讲话
and this is the first time I feel like I'm talking to a real person.
而且你知道不 我喜欢他 他人不错
And you know what? I like him. He's a nice guy.
你真的这么想的?
You really think so?
是啊
Yes.
这我还真的不知道
I don't know.
我知道
I do.
你这小机器人不错嘛
Nice little bot you've got here.
这我知道
I'm aware.
- 这是干嘛用的? 转齿? - 对 3400转每分钟
- What's this do,spin? - Yep. At 3400 RPM.
它切钢就像切橡皮一样
It can cut through steel like it was wubber.
赞
Neat.
做得不错
Good work.
谢尔顿 我们要赶快取消
Sheldon,we've got to call this off.
不要 莱纳德
No,Leonard.
多少年了 像克里帕奇一样的无良恶霸 让我的生活悲惨不堪
For years,merciless thugs like Kripke have made my life a series of painful noogies
抓住手臂来回扭以产生剧痛
既被痛打又受尽凌辱 还有印第安刑
and humiliating wedgies and the insensitively named Indian burns.
这些就此打住!
That stops now.
可是谢尔顿 我们没可能的
But,Sheldon,we don't have a chance.
你现在能给这机器人改进的 就是给它遥控器换块新电池
The only improvement you were able to make on the robot was to put fresh batteries in the remote.
你没发觉的是克里帕奇有一个致命伤
What you fail to realize is Kripke suffers from a fatal flaw:
他对机器人大体积超能量的过度自信
overconfidence from his robot's massive size and its overwhelming power.
那不是过度自信 那叫观察
That's not overconfidence. That's observation.
信我 克里帕奇很快就会倒在 我的心理战上的 观察吧
Trust me,Kripke will fall easy prey to my psychological warfare. Observe.
克里帕奇
Kripke.
我想问下你的机器人准备好见它制作人没 不过既然你是他的制作人了
I would ask if your robot is prepared to meet its maker,but as you are its maker,
很明显你们是见过面了
clearly the two of you have met.
他脑子怎么鸟?
What is his pwoblem?
学绝地武士心理战还差得远 伙计
Way to bust out the Jedi mind tricks,dude.
我只是想确认下我们说好了
I just want to make sure that we're all clear.
按照标准机器人格斗联盟规则
Standard robotic fighting league rules apply.
你是疯了不成? 这是个街战
Are you cwazy? This is a stweet fight.
街战哪有什么规则的?
The stweet has no rules.
他说得对 莱纳德 一直到死为直
He's right,Leonard. The paradigm is to the death.
不过我现在给你们个机会承认 我是比你们优越
I will,however,give you the opportunity to concede my superiority now
然后把你的机器人给我当战利品
and offer me your robot as the spoils of war.
永远都没可能!
Never.
我宁愿猛械死都不要落到你手里
I'd rather see Monte dead than in your hands.
那真是小菜一碟
That could be easily arranged.
各就各位准备开始?
Ready,set,go?
来吧
Do it.
那好吧 预备 开始
All right then. Weady. Set. Go.
来吧 谢尔顿 你可以的
Come on,Sheldon,you got this.
当然 我们做好了万全准备 他怎么对我们都不怕
Indeed. We are prepared for anything he can throw at us.
这招是新的
That's new.
- 逃啊 猛械! 逃! - 闪啊 Mont!
- Run,Monte,run! - Go,Monte!
- 猛械! - 跑! 跑! 跑! 跑!
- Monte! - Go,go,go,go!
别伤害我们! 别伤害我们! 别伤害我们!
Don't hurt us,don't hurt us,don't hurt us!
好了 弥补儿时心灵创伤就到此为止了
Well,so much for making up for the emotional wounds of childhood.
是我干的
I did this.
猛械被杀都是因为我的傲慢跟自大
Monte was killed by my hubris and my pride.
不管别人怎么说 这都是我的错
No matter what anybody says,this is my fault.
又没人在跟你争
No one's arguing with you,dude.
我收到你短信了 它有多烂... 噢
I got your text. How bad is... Oy.
先别管那机器人了 你是怎么了?
Forget the robot. What happened to you?
他不小心滑倒了
He slipped and fell.
是 我不小心滑倒了 还是在浴室里
Yes,I slipped and fell. In the bathroom.
被浴缸弹起来了
Bounced right off the tub.
对 现在他知道了 如果他不尊重浴缸的话 浴缸会给他好看的
Yes,now he knows what bathtubs are capable of doing when you don't treat them with respect.
那是
Yeah.
趁你闭眼时就给你一拳
They sucker punch you when your eyes are closed.
你觉得怎样 霍华德?
So what do you think,Howard?
也不算很烂 对吧?
It's not that bad,right?
噢 不算 用点电线包布 一些焊剂... 你是疯了还是怎样?!
Oh,no. A little electrical tape,some solder... Are you insane?
太空探测器坠毁在沙漠都比这死相好看
I've seen space probes that crashed into the desert that were in better shape than this.
你说得对 猛械走了
You're right. Monte's gone.
我们明早去埋了它 做个简单的仪式 我来主持
We'll bury him in the morning. A simple ceremony. I'll speak.
莱纳德 你要拉你的大提琴
Leonard,you'll play your cello.
谢尔顿 亲爱的 你是不是有点走火入魔了?
Sheldon,honey,aren't you getting a little carried away?
我是说 这不就是个机器人嘛
I mean,it's just a toy robot.
不就是个机器人嘛?
Just a toy robot?
佩妮
Penny.
我知道了 这就去
I know,I got it.
谢尔顿 对不起
Sheldon,I'm sorry.
别以为我吃亏了
Well,don't get the wrong idea.
在我看来 她很快就会因为同情 然后跟我做爱了
The way I see it,I'm halfway to pity sex.